http://www.benchmarkmedia.com/pages/privacy-policy

Benchmark Media Systems Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from benchmarkmedia.com (the Site).
HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PAYMENT INFORMATION
Benchmark uses Payment Providers that have secure access to credit card numbers or other methods of payment. Benchmark does not store and cannot view or retrieve credit card numbers, expiration dates, or security codes (these are collected directly by the Payment Providers at the time of checkout). We refer to this information as “Payment Information". Our Payment Providers include Shopify Payments, PayPal, and Amazon Pay. Payment Information is only used to collect the payment for your order and to issue refunds. For your protection, we cannot add additional charges after you place an order.
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, and method of payment (excluding credit card numbers, expiration dates, and security codes). We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
Other Information You Voluntarily Provide
If you sign up for our "Application Notes" the information you provide will be used for the purpose of sending periodic Application Note emails and will not be used for any other type of email or mailing and will not be provided to third parties.
If you provide a product review, we will ask for your email address so that we can authenticate the posting and contact you when you review has posted. We will not disclose your email address or use this collection for any other purpose. You have the option of posting your name, city, and country if you wish. If you post these by mistake, please contact us and we will remove these at your request.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
Communicate with you; Screen our Orders for potential risk or fraud; and when in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
We may use the Order Information to validate Warranty claims.
We may use the Order Information to confirm that product reviews were posted by actual customers.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
We may use your device information to provide advertising on websites that you visit in the future.
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
OPTING OUT
You can opt out of targeted advertising by entering a request at these links:FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=adsGOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymousBING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-adsAdditionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
EUROPEAN RESIDENTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at sales@benchmarkmedia.com or by mail using the details provided below:Benchmark Media Systems, Inc.203 E HAMPTON PLSYRACUSE, NY, 13206, United States
